hey this is Ryan I'm going to show you
嘿，这是瑞安，我要告诉你
really quickly how to get a new drop
真的很快如何获得新的一滴
wizard service up and running using
使用以下命令启动并运行向导服务
nothing more than IntelliJ and a little
只不过是IntelliJ而已
bit of knowledge on how drops root
关于如何扎根的一点知识
itself works so the first thing you want
本身可以工作，所以您想要的第一件事
to do is you're going to want to open up
你要做的就是要开放
IntelliJ if you don't have IntelliJ go
IntelliJ（如果您没有IntelliJ）
to the JetBrains website and get
到JetBrains网站并获得
yourself a copy of community edition
自己是社区版的副本
it's free and has everything that you
它是免费的，并拥有您所拥有的一切
need if you want later on you can
需要，如果你想以后可以
splurge the two hundred dollars for a
挥霍两百美元
personal license for ultimate but
最终许可证
community is version to get started so
社区是开始的版本，因此
we're going to start by creating a new
我们将从创建一个新的开始
project you're going to want to make
您要制作的项目
sure that you have maven module selected
确保您已选择Maven模块
once you have that go and give it a
一旦拥有了，给它一个
project name call it drop wizard demo
项目名称调用放置向导演示
this is going to create the directory
这将创建目录
Matilda I want the one seven SDK it's
Matilda我想要一个七个SDK
then going to ask you for a group ID the
然后要问你一个组ID
amur drivers are demo I personally like
我个人喜欢阿穆尔车司机的演示
to start with a point of one snapshot
从一个快照开始
doesn't really matter as your version
与您的版本无关紧要
you can see there's some archetype
你可以看到有一些原型
support here we've tried building
在这里我们尝试建立支持
archetypes in the past they are really
过去的原型确实是
really hard to do they're hard to do
真的很难做，他们很难做
well they're a pain and doing this
好吧，他们很痛苦，这样做
inside of IntelliJ really takes no time
IntelliJ内部真的不需要时间
at all you click finish and mavens going
在所有您单击完成，行家走了
to go ahead to me drop Wizard IntelliJ
继续给我放下向导IntelliJ
is going to go and set up a basic
将要去建立一个基本的
project structure for you you can have
您可以拥有的项目结构
all your basic directories are here your
您所有的基本目录都在这里
pom is here this is where you're going
pom在这里，这就是你要去的地方
to get started with all maven projects
开始所有Maven项目
you're going to have dependencies so
你将有依赖性，所以
we're just going to start there and I'm
我们只是要从那里开始，我是
going to tell it that I want to auto
告诉我我要自动
import all the palm changes maven has or
导入Maven拥有的所有手掌更改或
IntelliJ has some really nice smart
IntelliJ有一些非常好的智能
templates support in this case it has
在这种情况下，模板支持
smart temple support for dependencies
智能寺庙支持依赖性
inside of maven pom files so I can just
在maven pom文件中，所以我可以
type in DEP and then tab and it's going
输入DEP，然后按Tab即可
to fill in the scaffolding for me and
为我填充脚手架
then at this point will tell me which
那么这时会告诉我
artifacts it knows about and I'll just
它知道的文物，我只是
start typing in drop wizard and select
开始输入放置向导并选择
core and it knows drop was a core as
核心，并且知道drop是核心
part of commune or drop wizard and at
公社或放置向导的一部分，并在
this point it also knows that certain
这一点它也知道
versions are available to me this tends
我倾向于使用版本
to be mostly based on what you actually
主要取决于您的实际情况
have in your local maven repo IntelliJ
在本地Maven存储库IntelliJ中
is a
是一个
the brain dead when it comes to actually
实际上，大脑死了
going out to mavin repose to scan for
出去让马文休息一下
versions will tell Utley 106 - and you
版本会告诉Utley 106-而您
can see it really quickly pulled in the
可以看到它真的很快拉入
dependencies and it's all ready to go
依赖关系，一切准备就绪
now
现在
so then close the pawn file and now
所以关闭pawn文件
we're going to create a new java class
我们将创建一个新的java类
over here and drop of the third demo dot
在这里并放下第三个演示点
sample service so this will create a new
样本服务，因此这将创建一个新的
sample service get rid of the
样品服务摆脱了
boilerplate there sample service it's
样板服务
drop lizard service so it needs to
放下蜥蜴服务，因此需要
extend service you want the droplet
扩展您想要的服务
service not the other services and
服务而不是其他服务
service itself is templatized so we're
服务本身是模板化的，所以我们
going to want a sample configuration
想要一个样本配置
sample configuration doesn't exist so it
样本配置不存在，因此它
highlights red one nice thing in
突出红色的一件好事
IntelliJ is it has sort of fix it for me
IntelliJ对我来说可以修复它吗
type dialogues if you press at least in
如果您至少按下则输入对话
my key bindings it's option enter it'll
我的键绑定选项输入
bring up this nice menu of options here
在这里调出这个不错的选项菜单
in this case it sees that the class
在这种情况下，它会看到
doesn't exist and gives me the option to
不存在，让我可以选择
create it as an interface an enum or
将其创建为枚举或接口
what I want which is actually a class
我想要的实际上是一堂课
and ask me what package I wanted to go
问我我想去什么包裹
in that's fine or boilerplate to nuke
在那很好或者样板
and at this point we know it's drop
在这一点上，我们知道它正在下降
wizard so you want to extend
向导，所以你想扩展
configuration select the drop wizard
配置选择放置向导
configuration most services will have
大多数服务将具有的配置
additional configuration here for the
此处的其他配置
purposes of a sample it's sufficient
样品的目的就足够了
just to extend the base configuration
只是为了扩展基本配置
you see it's still complaining about
你看到它还在抱怨
some stuff here so we can option enter
一些东西在这里，所以我们可以选择输入
again until it that we want to implement
再次直到我们要实施
methods basically it's detecting some
方法基本上是在检测一些
abstract methods and service I haven't
我没有的抽象方法和服务
been implemented yet so we'll go ahead
已经实施，所以我们继续
and add those and initialize and run or
并添加它们并初始化并运行或
what we'll have to implement take out
我们将要实施的内容
some more boilerplate here the boiler
这里还有一些样板
plates coming from IntelliJ if you want
如果需要，可以从IntelliJ获得板
you can dig in and change the templates
您可以挖掘并更改模板
for what actually gets dumped into there
实际扔到那里的东西
I don't bother we can once again use
我不打扰我们可以再次使用
another smart template in IntelliJ PS VM
IntelliJ PS VM中的另一个智能模板
which is shorthand for public static
这是public static的简写
void main if I type that in and hit tab
如果我在其中键入内容并点击选项卡，则void main
it'll automatically fill in a main
它会自动填写一个主
method for me so we'll say a new sample
我的方法，所以我们说一个新的样本
service run args I'm running through the
服务运行参数我正在运行
drop wizard stuff a little bit quickly
快速删除向导的内容
cuz I'm hoping that
因为我希望
people will mostly have either built
人们大多都会建
services or will have at least looked at
服务或至少已经看过
the QuickStart documentation the coda
快速入门文档的尾声
put together on drop wizard coda he'll
放在一起放下巫师尾声
calm in this case it's still complaining
在这种情况下，它仍然很抱怨
about an exception that's being thrown
关于正在引发的异常
so option enter again exception of
所以选项再次输入
method signature and now there's no more
方法签名，现在没有了
complaints at this point we're going to
在这一点上，我们要投诉
need a sample configuration file for
需要一个样本配置文件
this so it is sample ml put this on top
这是样品毫升放在上面
level directory the only thing you need
唯一需要的级别目录
to get started is just the HTTP port
开始只是HTTP端口
configuration so put the HTTP on 8080 in
配置，因此将HTTP放在8080中
the admin port on 8081 and close that
在8081上的管理端口并关闭
now one of the nice thing in IntelliJ is
现在IntelliJ中的一件好事是
I can go to the service class over here
我可以去这里的服务班
in the project view I can right click on
在项目视图中，我可以右键单击
it and select create sample service main
它并选择创建样本服务主
and I can tell it the program arguments
我可以告诉它程序参数
are server sample yeah Mel and that'll
是服务器样本，是的，梅尔，那会
tell that those are the command-line
告诉那些是命令行
parameters to pass to it when it runs
运行时传递给它的参数
and when I do this it'll actually create
当我这样做时，它实际上会创建
a run profile top for me and I can
我的跑步资料上衣，我可以
either run it or I can debug it I always
要么运行它，要么我可以调试它，
like to run stuff in the debugger
喜欢在调试器中运行东西
inevitably I'm going to watch a debug so
不可避免地，我将观看调试，因此
go ahead and click run it's going to
继续并单击“运行”
compile and then it'll start running and
编译，然后它将开始运行并
we'll get there's a stack trace here
我们会在这里找到堆栈跟踪
it's complaining that there's no root
抱怨没有根
resource that's been created so let's
已创建的资源，所以让我们
create one really quickly we'll say over
快速创建一个，我们会说一遍
here environment add resource new hello
这里环境添加资源新的你好
world resource the class doesn't exist
该类不存在的世界资源
so option enter again create class
所以选择再次输入创建类
HelloWorld resource I like to put it in
我喜欢将HelloWorld资源放入其中
the resources package it's just me so
资源包就是我自己
that gets created over here and it
在这里创建它
forces a jax-rs resource so we're going
强制使用jax-rs资源，所以我们要
to give it a path greetings
给它一个路径的问候
name and we're going to add a method to
名称，我们将添加一个方法
handle the get methods public string get
处理get方法public string get
routine path per am name string name i'm
每个我的例行路径名称字符串名称
just going to return
刚要回来
hello I can type give an exclamation
你好，我可以输入一个感叹号
point we're really happy to see this
我们很高兴看到这一点
person now that all gets cleared up now
现在的人，现在一切都清除了
one nice thing and IntelliJ is there's
一件好事，IntelliJ是
just this little recycle button here or
只是这里的这个小回收按钮
rerun you can click that it'll recompile
重新运行，您可以单击它将重新编译
and rerun you don't have to click stop
并重新运行，您无需单击停止
and then run saves it an extra second or
然后运行可将其保存额外的一秒钟或
two and now you can see we actually have
两个，现在你可以看到我们实际上有
the resource so we'll jump over to the
资源，所以我们将跳转到
browser go to localhost 8080 readings
浏览器转到localhost 8080读数
Orion and we get back hello Ryan if we
猎户座，如果我们
want we can jump back over to drop
希望我们可以跳回去
wizard we can go to the resource and I
向导，我们可以去资源，我
can set a breakpoint right here in this
可以在这里设置断点
method go back to the browser reload and
方法返回到浏览器重新加载，
it will automatically pop the browser
它将自动弹出浏览器
open it's at the breakpoint you can see
打开它在您可以看到的断点处
we have the resource we have the
我们有资源，我们有
incoming parameter over here you can see
您可以在此处看到传入参数
the entire call stack and if I want I
整个通话堆栈，如果我愿意的话
can actually jump up the call stack to
实际上可以跳到调用堆栈
see what was going on at each one of
看看每一个发生了什么
these points you can see all the local
这些点你可以看到所有本地
variables I can mess with things or if I
变量，我会弄乱东西，或者如果我
want I can just come back at the top
希望我能回到顶部
here and I can click run the step
在这里，我可以单击运行步骤
through it and the value comes back
通过它，价值又回来了
again and that's it that's a running
再次，就是这样运行
drop lizard application in a few minutes
在几分钟内放下蜥蜴应用程序
prove to you really quickly that it's
很快向您证明这是
really a maven project the CD drop
真正的Maven项目CD放下
wizard demo I see call my project files
向导演示，我看到调用了我的项目文件
are in here there's the palm and I can
在这里，有手掌，我可以
run maven clean compile and there you go
运行Maven Clean编译，然后就可以了
you'll need to add in all the stuff for
您需要添加所有内容
doing your builds including resources
进行包括资源在内的构建
and stuff like that but that should be
和类似的东西，但那应该是
fairly trivial to follow along from
相当简单
another example right
另一个例子吧